Sameer Kamran

Lahore, Pakistan sameerkamrandev@gmail.com | +923124738908



An innovative and ambitious engineer with experience in Web/Mobile App Development, Design and Database Development. In the beginning of my degree i worked on few wordpress blogs as i have great interest in this field. Then i decided to take it as my career. Im a strong team player, communicator, leader, problem-solver and decision maker with excellent experience within the diverse companies, Sound knowledge of various cultures and English language skills.

Skills

.Net Core

Angular2+

ASP.Net

Bootstrap

C#

git

Jquery

NodelS

Education

University of the Punjab

BS(Information Technology), Information Technology | Lahore

December 2017 | 3.1 CGPA

Govt. College Science, Wahdat Rd

F.Sc. (Pre-Engg), Science | Lahore November 2013 | 76%

Unique High School

Matriculation, Science | Lahore August 2011 | 75%

Certifications

Certified Asp Dot Net Specialist

E-Venture Solutions Starting March 2017

Functional Areas

Software & Web Development

Industries

Information Technology

Professional Experience | 3 Years

Dot Net / Angular Developer

Boltech Solutions | Lahore, Pakistan

Jun 2019 - Present

My responsibilities here, are to design databases, build RESTFul Api End-Points, creating client apps using Angular, that consumes those apis. I am also the part of requirement gathering team and engaged directly with clients for turning their demands into working softwares.

Software Engineer

Codility Solutions | Lahore, Pakistan

Oct 2017 - Jun 2019

Quite good company,worked in a proper agile environment,learnt alot by facing healthy challenges daily.

Worked on Asp Net Core, Asp Net MVC5, WPF, Xamarin, MEAN Stack, and other techs.

Junior Web Developer

Inseparable Technology PVT. LTD | Lahore, Pakistan

May 2017 - Aug 2017

Learnt alot here, Contributed in their core project as a backend developer, using Asp Net MVC5, SingalR, Quartz. Net and other tools.

Customer Service Representative

Telco Communications PVT. LTD. | Lahore, Pakistan

Nov 2014 - Aug 2016

It was a great positive experience, learnt alot from there, polished my communication skills and english vocabulary and made many good friends.

Projects

Expeni

May 2018 - Present

Expeni Ivc

http://app.expeni.com

Tools: Asp .Net Core & MVC5, KnockoutJS,

Attendance Management System

Codility Solutions

Mar 2018 - Apr 2018

Tools: Asp .Net MVC5 ,Bootstrap,Entity Framework, Jquery

Employees have their logins, They can mark their attendances and can add their daily tasks which they have done.

Admin can see all the activities, generate the reports on specified-time basis. Cron Jobs are running to automate the tasks.

This system is currently running locally.

Service360 Nov 2017 - Dec 2017

Service360

http://www.service360fyp.somee.com

Tools: Visual Studio, MS SQL Server Management Studio

Its my Final Year Project.It is actually a website which will help people to request a Maintenance Worker or Handyman to their place from our company. ASP .Net Framework (MVC5) ,Bootstrap,Jquery, and other technologies are used in this project

if you want to have see a demo .then.

Admin Login: User: smrkamran Pass: sameer786 Customer Login: User: wasi Pass: wasi786

Languages Hobbies

English - Native Football
Urdu - Native Movies
Punjabi - Medium Songs

Songs Cycling Coding

